Guide to the Bruce J. Zobel Papers, 1937-2008 MC 00259
Special Collections Research Center
- Reports, 1952-2005; MC 00259 Series 10
  - Topical Reports
    - Dendrology and Species
      - "Giant Leucaena (Koa Haole) Energy Tree Farm: An Economic Feasibility Analysis for the Island of Molokai, Hawaii," by Molokai Study Team, Hawaii Natural Energy Institute, University of Hawaii at Manoa, September, 1980; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - "Subdivisions of the Genus PINUS (Pines)," by Elbert L. Little, Jr. and William B. Critchfield, US Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, December, 1969; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - "Geographic Distribution of the Pines of the World," by William B. Critchfield and Elbert L. Little, Jr., US Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, February, 1966; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 11)
      - "The Pines of Mexico and British Honduras: A Report on a Reconnaissance of Mexico and British Honduras during 1947," by E.E.M. Loock, Department of Forestry, Union of South Africa, undated; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 12)
      - "Genetics of Lodgepole Pine," US Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, November, 1980; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 13)
      - "Sweetgum... an American Wood," by C.B. Briscoe, US Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, July, 1973; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 14)
      - "A Selected and Annotated Bibliography of Pitch Pine (Pinus rigida Mill.)," by Silas Little, Jack McCormick, and John W. Andresen, US Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, 1970; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 15)
      - "Guide to Alaska Trees," by Leslie A. Viereck and Elbert L. Little, Jr., US Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, December, 1974; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 16)
      - "Forest Trees of Texas: How to Know Them," Sixth Edition, Texas Forest Service, September, 1953; Formerly Box 61P (Box 103, Folder 17)
      - 1, Mexican Pines report, [no date]; Formerly Box 61Q (Box 104)
      - 2, "Yellow-Poplar (Liriodendron tulipifera): An Annotated Bibliography," Compiled by Roland E. Schoenike, Department of Forestry, Clemson University; Formerly Box 61Q (Box 104)
        July, 1980
      - 3, "Choosing Scots pine (Pinus sylvestris L.) provenances in Northern Sweden: analysis of survival, growth and quality in provenance experiments planted 1951," by Jan Remrod, Department of Forest Genetics, Royal College of Forestry, Stockholm; Formerly Box 61Q (Box 104)
        1976
      - 4, "Los Arboles Mas Importantes de la Serrania de San Lucas," by Humberto Jimenez, Instituto de Desarrollo de los Recursos Naturales Renovables, Colombia; Formerly Box 61Q (Box 104)
        1970
    - Disease
      - "Index of Hosts and Associated Fungi Identified by the Forest Insect and Disease Survey in Ontario from 1967 to 1987: I. The Pines," by D.T. Myren and C.N. Davis, Great Lakes Forestry Centre, 1989; Formerly Box 61R (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - "Forest Disease Research in the Western United States and British Columbia, Canada," by Thomas S. Buchanan, U.S. Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, Southeastern Forest Experiment Station, September, 1976; Formerly Box 61R (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Diversity
      - "Technologies to Maintain Biological Diversity," Congress of the United States, Office of Technology Assessment, March, 1987; Formerly Box 61R (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Eucalypts
      - "O Reflorestamento Com Eucalipto e Seus Impactos Ambientais," by Walter de Paula Lima, Artpress, 1987; Formerly Box 61R (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - "Eucalypts for West Africa," by K. Kadambi, reprinted from Advancing Frontiers of Plant Sciences, Vol. 24, undated; Formerly Box 61R (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - "Instrucoes para o plantio do ecucalypto (Instructions about the planting of the Eucalyptus)," by Armando Navarro Sampaio, 1952; Formerly Box 61R (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - "O Eucalipto e a Ecologia," Aracruz, 1975; Formerly Box 61R (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - "Annotated bibliography on environmental, social and economic impacts of eucalypts," Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations, 1995; Formerly Box 61R (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - "Integrated Studies: Factors Contributing to the Strength Properties of a Sheet of Paper," Project 1513, Progress Report Sixteen to Pulp Evaluation Group, Institute of Paper Chemistry, February 25, 1957; Formerly Box 61R (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - "Estudo da Variacao da Densidade Basica da Madeira de Eucalyptus Alba Reinw E Eucalyptus Saligna Smith," by Mario Ferreira, Piracicaba, 1968; Formerly Box 61R (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - "Handbook of Forestry in Victoria," prepared for the Forests Comission, Victoria, by K.V.M> Ferguson, 1965; Formerly Box 61S (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - "Aspectos do Emprego de Fertilizantes Minerais No Reflorestamento de Solos de Cerrado Do Estado de Sao Paulo Com Eucalyptus saligna Sm.," by Helladio Do Amaral Mello, Universidade de Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1968; Formerly Box 61S (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - "The Ecological Effects of Eucalyptus," by M.E.D. Poore and C. Fries, FAO Forestry Paper 59, Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations, 1989; Formerly Box 61S (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - "The Eucalyptus Energy Farm - Feasibility Study and Demonstration Phase 1: Site and Species Selection," prepared for U.S. Department of Energy, June, 1978; Formerly Box 61S (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - "Programme of the Introduction of Species and Provenances of Eucalyptus spp in Brazil", undated; Formerly Box 61S (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - "O Que o Eucalipto Pode Fazer Pelo Brasil," by Maxwell R. Jacobs, Projeto de Desenvolvimento e Pesquisa Florestal, Serie Tecnica, undated; Formerly Box 61S (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - "Field Guide to the Eucalypts of the Gympie, Imbil and Maryborough Forestry Districts," by M. Podberscek, Queensland Forest Service, Technical Paper No. 48, 1991; Formerly Box 61S (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - "Apectos Principais de Estudo Sobre Pragas de Eucalipto," Projeto de Desenvolvimento e Pesquisa Florestal, Comunicacao Tecnica No. 4, December 10, 1976; Formerly Box 61S (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - "An Annotated Bibliography of Genetic Variation in Eucalyptus Camaldulensis," compiled by K.G. Eldridge, Commmonwealth Forestry Institute and CSIR Tropical Forestry Papers, No. 8, 1975; Formerly Box 61S (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - "The Natural Occurrence of the Eucalypts," prepared by N. Hall, R.D. Johnston, and Rosemary Marryatt, Forest Research Institute, Commonwealth of Australia, Department of National Development, Forestry and Timber Bureau, 1963; Formerly Box 61S (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Report by Wayne Tibbits, The Winston Churchill Memorial Trust of Australia, 1990 (Box 382, Folder 10)
    - Genetics
      - "International Training Course in Forest Tree Breeding: Selected Reference Papers," by the Australian Development Assistance Agency, 1978; Formerly Box 61S (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - "Tropical Hardwood Genetics: Directory of Current Workers," Department of Biology, University of Massachusetts, April 1977; Formerly Box 61S (Box 106, Folder 12)
      - "Forest Tree Breeding and Genetics," by R.H. Richens, Imperial Agricultural Bureaux, Joint Publication No. 8, November 1, 1945; Formerly Box 61T (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - "Report on the Training Centre on Forest Tree Improvement," Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations, 1970; Formerly Box 61T (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - "Bibliography of Australian Forest Tree Improvement and Forest Genetics 1937 to 1972," by K.G. Eldridge, Technical Note No. 4, Forestry and Timber Bureau, Australia, 1973; Formerly Box 61T (Box 107, Folder 3)
      - "Introduction to Practical Forest Tree Improvement," Forest Genetics Laboratory, Texas Forest Service, August, 1971; Formerly Box 61T (Box 107, Folder 4)
      - "The Methodology of Conservation of Forest Genetic Resources: Report on a Pilot Study," Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations, 1975; Formerly Box 61T (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - "Radiata Pine Breeding Manual," edited by A.C. Matheson and A.G. Brown, Division of Forest Research, CSIRO, Australia, 1983; Formerly Box 61T (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - "Forest Genetics Research in the Rocky Mountain and Pacific Coast States and British Columbia," Report of a Survey by the Forest Genetics Research Foundation, November, 1958; Formerly Box 61T (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Herbicides
      - "A Guide to Silvicultural Herbicide Use in the Southern United States," by Rick L. Cantrell, Auburn University School of Forestry and Alabama Agricultural Experiment Station, November, 1985; Formerly Box 61T (Box 107, Folder 8)
      - "Single Tree Spray Systems: Progress Report," USDA Forest Service, Technology and Development Program, November, 1995; Formerly Box 61T (Box 107, Folder 9)
      - "Benefits of 2,4,5-T in Forest Management," American Paper Institute/National Forest Products Association, October, 1978; Formerly Box 61T (Box 107, Folder 10)
      - "Auburn University Silvicultural Herbicide Cooperative, 1983-84 Report," Alabama Agricultural Experiment Station, School of Forestry, November, 1985; Formerly Box 61T (Box 107, Folder 11)
      - "Auburn University Forestry Chemicals Cooperative: 1977 Annual Report," Agricultural Experiment Station, Department of Forestry, Auburn University, undated; Formerly Box 61U (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Japan and Korea
      - Japanese report (not translated), Formerly Box 61U (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - "1970 Annual Report of the Hokkaido Branch, Government Forest Experiment Station," Sapporo, Japan, October, 1971; Formerly Box 61U (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - "1973 Annual Report of the Hokkaido Branch, Government Forest Experiment Station," Sapporo, Japan, September, 1974; Formerly Box 61U (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - "1982 Annual Report, Kanto Forest Tree Breeding Institute," Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries, Mito, Japan, January, 1984; Formerly Box 61U (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - "1983 Annual Report, Kanto Forest Tree Breeding Institute," Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries, Mito, Japan, January, 1985; Formerly Box 61U (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - "1988 Annual Report, Kanto Forest Tree Breeding Institute," Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries, Mito, Japan, March, 1990; Formerly Box 61U (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - "1990 Annual Report, Kanto Forest Tree Breeding Institute," Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries, Mito, Japan, March, 1992; Formerly Box 61U (Box 108, Folder 8)
      - "Collection of Theses Published by Professor Sin Kyu Hyun Compiled In Commemoration of His Sixtieth Birthday," Committee on Commemoration for the Sixtieth Birthday of Professor Sin Kyu Hyun, January 24, 1972; Formerly Box 61U (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 22, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, 1986; Formerly Box 61U (Box 108, Folder 10)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 23, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, 1987; Formerly Box 61U (Box 108, Folder 11)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 24, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, 1988; Formerly Box 61U (Box 108, Folder 12)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 16, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, December, 1980; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 18, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, December, 1982; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 18, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, December, 1982; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 19, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, December, 1983; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 20, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, December, 1984; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 21, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, December, 1985; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 5)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 27, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, December, 1991; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 6)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 5, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, December, 1967; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 7)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 6, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, December, 1968; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 8)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 9, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, July, 1972; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 9)
      - "Research Report of the Institute of Forest Genetics," No. 15, Institute of Forest Genetics, Forestry Administration, Suwon, Korea, December, 1979; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 10)
      - "1996 Annual Report of Hokkaido Research Center Forestry and Forest Products Research Institute," Sapporo, Japan, August, 1997; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Pests
      - "Insectos de Conos y Semillas de las Coniferas de Mexico (Cone and Seed Insects of the Mexican Conifers)," by David Cibrian-Tovar, Bernard H. Ebel, Harry O. Yates III, and Jose Tulio Mendez-Montiel, United States Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, Southeastern Forest Experiment Station, 1986; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 12)
      - "Conifer Cone and Seed Pests," by G.V. Stadnitskii, G.I. Iurchenko, A.N. Smetanin, V.P. Grebenshchikova, and M.V. Pribylova, translated from Russian and edited by Harry O. Yates, III, undated; Formerly Box 61V (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Physiology
      - "Five-Year Growth Responses Following Fertilization and Thinning of Loblolly Pine Stands," NCSFFC Report No. 15, North Carolina State Forest Fertilization Cooperative, School of Forest Resources, NCSU, May, 1984; Formerly Box 61W (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - "Tree Physiology Bibliography," compiled by Theodore T. Kozlowski of the University of Massachusetts, Amherst, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, November, 1958; Formerly Box 61W (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Politics of Forestry
      - "Towards a Sustainable Paper Cycle," International Institute for Environment and Development, 1996; Formerly Box 61W (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - "Sustaining Profits and Forests: the Business of Sustainable Forestry," the John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1997; Formerly Box 61W (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - "A National Program for Assessing the Problem of Atmospheric Deposition (Acid Rain): A Report to the Council on Environmental Quality," National Atmospheric Deposition Program, NC-141, December, 1978; Formerly Box 61W (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Silviculture and Forest Management
      - "Canada's Threatened Forests: A Statement by the Science Council," Science Council of Canada, March, 1983; Formerly Box 61W (Box 110, Folder 6)
      - "Forest Management in Canada, Volume I," F.L.C. Reed and Associates Ltd., Forest Management Institute, Information Report FMR-X-102, January, 1978; Formerly Box 61W (Box 110, Folder 7)
      - "Forest Management in Canada, Volume II: Case Studies," F.L.C. Reed and Associates Ltd., Forest Management Institute, Information Report FMR-X-103, January, 1978; Formerly Box 61W (Box 110, Folder 8)
      - "Radial Growth in Tree Roots: Distribution, Timing, Anatomy," D.C.F. Fayle, Technical Report No. 9, University of Toronto, Faculty of Forestry, 1968; Formerly Box 61W (Box 110, Folder 9)
      - "Summary of the Report to the Congress on Forestry on Tropical Degraded Lands: Implications for Operational Forest Programs," by Gary R. Hodge, April 11, 1983; Formerly Box 61W (Box 110, Folder 10)
      - "Ecological Aspects of Development in the Humid Tropics," National Academy Press, 1982; Formerly Box 61W (Box 110, Folder 11)
      - "An Update (1970/71-1982) of the Annotated Bibliography on Initial Tree Spacing," F. Evert, Information Report PI-X-44, Petawawa National Forestry Institute, 1984; Formerly Box 61X (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - "Annotated Bibliography on Initial Tree Spacing," F. Evert, Information Report FMR-X-50, Forest Management Institute, Canadian Forestry Service, April, 1973; Formerly Box 61X (Box 111, Folder 2)
      - "The South's Fourth Forest: Alternatives for the Future--Review Draft," United States Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, circa 1980s; Formerly Box 61X (Box 111, Folder 3)
      - "Assessment of Promising Forest Management Practices and Technologies for Enhancing the Conservation and Sequestration of Atmospheric Carbon and Their Costs at the Site Level," United States Environmental Protection Agency, October, 1991; Formerly Box 61X (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - Untitled Reports about Sudan, printed by the Arabic Printer House, undated; Formerly Box 61X (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - "Pubblicazioni del Centro di Sperimentazione Agricola e Forestale," Ente Nazionale per la Cellulosa e Per La Carta, Volume IV, 1960; Formerly Box 61X (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - "Root deformation of forest tree seedlings - proceedings of a nordic symposium," the Swedish University of Agricultural Sciences, Department of Forest Yield Research, Report No. 11, 1982; Formerly Box 61X (Box 111, Folder 7)
      - "Availability of Hardwoods in the Lower Atlantic and Gulf Coastal Plains," Hardwood Research Program, North Carolina State University, February 14, 1985; Formerly Box 61X (Box 111, Folder 8)
      - "A Preliminary Silvicultural Classification of Malawi," Forestry Research Institute of Malawi, 1978; Formerly Box 61Y (Box 112, Folder 1)
      - "Cultural Treatment Effects on Growth of Four-Year Old Loblolly Pine," NCSFFC Report No. 18, NC State Forest Fertilization Cooperative, 1985; Formerly Box 61Y (Box 112, Folder 2)
      - "A Guide for Revegetating Coal Mine Soils in the Eastern United States," by Willis G. Vogel, USDA Forest Service, Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, General Technical Report NE-68, 1981; Formerly Box 61Y (Box 112, Folder 3)
      - "Intensive Plantation Culture: Five Years Research," USDA Forest Service, North Central Forest Experiment Station, General Technical Report NC-21, 1976; Formerly Box 61Y (Box 112, Folder 4)
      - "Effects of Land Use on Municipal Watersheds," by T. Ewald Maki and William L. Hafley, Water Resources Research Institute of the University of North Carolina, Report No. 71, July, 1972; Formerly Box 61Y (Box 112, Folder 5)
      - "Precommercial thinning speeds growth and development of lodgepole pine: 25-year results," by W.D. Johnstone, Northern Forest Research Centre, Edmonton, Alberta, Information Report NOR-X-237, 1981; Formerly Box 61Y (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - "Annotated Bibliography on Initial Tree Spacing," by F. Evert, Forest Management Institute, Ottawa, Ontario, Information Report FMR-X-50, Project Number 86, Canadian Forestry Service, Department of the Environment, July, 1977; Formerly Box 61Y (Box 112, Folder 7)
      - "Spacing Studies - A Review," by F. Evert, Forest Management Institute, Ottawa, Ontario, Information Report FMR-X-37, Canadian Forestry Service, Department of the Environment, December, 1971; Formerly Box 61Y (Box 112, Folder 8)
      - "Forestry in Romania," by Filip Tomulescu, Ministry of Agriculture, Food, Industry, Silviculture and Waters, Department of Silviculture, 1971; Formerly Box 61Y (Box 112, Folder 9)
      - "Technologies for Reforestation of Degraded Lands in the Tropics," by Carl M. Gallegos, Charles B. Davey, Robert L. Kellison, Pedro A. Sanchez, and Bruce J. Zobel, undated; Formerly Box 61Y (Box 112, Folder 10)
      - "Chromosome aberrations in stored seeds of Pinus silvestris and Picea abies and the consequences on plant properties," by Milan Simak, Swedish University of Agricultural Sciences, Department of Silviculture, Rapporter No. 20, 1986 (Box 382, Folder 11)
    - South Africa
      - "Report for 1978-1979 (Thirty-Second Year)," Wattle Research Institute, University of Natal, Pietermaritzburg, South Africa, October, 1979; Formerly Box 61Z (Box 113, Folder 1)
      - "Report for 1982-1983 (Thirty-Sixth Year)," Wattle Research Institute, University of Natal, Pietermaritzburg, South Africa, October, 1983; Formerly Box 61Z (Box 113, Folder 2)
      - "Report for 1983-1984 (Thirty-Seventh Year)," Wattle Research Institute, University of Natal, Pietermaritzburg, South Africa, September, 1984; Formerly Box 61Z (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Utilization of Wood
      - "La Variabilite du Bois," by Gerard Nepveu, Station de Recherches sur la Qualite des Bois, Institut National de la Recherche Agronomique, Centre de Recherches Forestieres de Nancy, October, 1991; Formerly Box 61Z (Box 113, Folder 4)
      - "The Potential of Loblolly Pine (Pinus taeda L.) for Producing Cellulose for Industrial Uses," by Donald E. Cole, Special Report, School of Forestry Resources, North Carolina State University, December, 1974; Formerly Box 61Z (Box 113, Folder 5)
      - "Suitability of Selected North Carolina Hardwoods for Bleachable Kraft Pulping," by J.A. Merricks and L.K. Semke, Pulpwood Evaluation Program, Report No. 9, Riegel Paper Corporation, Pulp and Paperboard Division, Riegelwood, North Carolina, March 9, 1967; Formerly Box 62A (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Vegetative Propagation
      - "Micropropagation D'Arbres Forestiers," AFOCEL, Etudes et Recherches, No. 12, June, 1979; Formerly Box 62B (Box 115, Folder 1)
      - "Die Fruhdiagnose in der Zuchtung und Zuchtungsforschung: Beitrage zur Methodik der Zuchtung langlebiger Pflanzen," Edited by H. Stubbe and W. Schmidt, Der Zuchter: Zeitschrift fur theoretische und angewandte Genetik. 4th Special Issue, 1957; Formerly Box 62B (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Wood, Emphasis on Biomass
      - "The History of Mechanical Pulping," by Charles H. Carpenter, written for the TAPPI Mechanical Pulping Committee, 1987; Formerly Box 62B (Box 115, Folder 3)
      - "Pinus Caribaea, Volume 2: Wood Properties," by R.A. Plumptre, Tropical Forestry Paper No. 17, Unit of Tropical Silviculture, Commonwealth Forestry Institute, University of Oxford, 1983; Formerly Box 62B (Box 115, Folder 4)
      - "The Potential of Eucalyptus for Producing Dry Matter for Industrial Uses," by Donald E. Cole, January, 1975; Formerly Box 62B (Box 115, Folder 5)
      - "Published and Unpublished Biomass Studies in the Nordic Countries: An Annotated Bibliography up to 1982," edited by Arne Albrektson, Helge Frivold, Helge Holstener-Jorgensen, and Eino Malkonen, Rapporter, No. 19, Swedishe University of Agricultural Sciences, Department of Silviculture, 1986; Formerly Box 62B (Box 115, Folder 6)
      - "Energy from Biomass for Developing Countries: A State of the Art Report," International Development Research Centre Manuscript Reports, IDRC-MR3, August, 1978; Formerly Box 62B (Box 115, Folder 7)
      - "Forest Biomass Energy Production--A Five Year Retrospect of the Work of Programme Group 'B'--IEA/FE," by L. Zsuffa and D. Morgan, Forestry Energy Agreement, International Energy Agency Programme Group B - Biomass Growth and Production, Ontario Tree Improvement and Forest Biomass Institute, 1983; Formerly Box 62B (Box 115, Folder 8)